http://www.msaltd.co.uk/policies/privacy-policy.aspx

This websites uses cookies, by continuing to browse the site you are agreeing to our use of cookies. View our privacy policy.
Forensic Chemistry
Atmospheric Pressure Chemical Ionisation (APCI)
Tandem Mass Spectrometry (MS-MS)
Thermal Desorption (TD)
Website Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Mass Spec Analytical Ltd uses and protects any information that you supply during your use of this website.
Mass Spec Analytical Ltd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Mass Spec Analytical Ltd may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1 May 2018.
What we collect
When you visit our website we may request that you provide personal information so we can maintain a record for you to enhance your experience with us.  This will include any information you voluntarily and automatically provide as detailed below.
We may periodically collect the following information:
Personal information, such as your name, email address, company name and phone number.
Demographic and navigational information, such as your IP address, geographic location, referral source, length of visit and pages viewed.
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
We will not collect any Sensitive information from you.
What we do with the information we gather
You can be assured that we will never sell your personal information on to any third party.
We require the information we collect in order to understand your needs and provide you with a better quality of service and with information you may find of interest, specifically with reference to the following:
Improvement of products and services
Supplying information that we think will be of interest to you via email and post; including news, advice and opinion, product and service details and promotions.
Periodically conducting market research, which may lead to enhancements of the website or changes to the content provided.
We employ the use of clear gifs (also known as web beacons) on our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened. This allows us to gauge how effective our communications are and is categorised as part of your personal information. To learn more about how you can control your personal information, please see below.
We will only hold this information for 3 years after which we will contact you again.
Security of your personal information
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect from you online,
When personal information (such as name, phone number, email address and/or geo-location data) is collected on our website, it is protected using encryption such as SSL (Secure Socket Layer).
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
In line with GDPR, whenever you are asked to fill in a form, you will have the option to confirm that you are happy for us to store your personal information and ‘opt out’ of any future communications from us if you wish.
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by emailing service@msaltd.co.uk
If you have provided us with personal information, you have the right to review it and request changes to be made or for it to be deleted.  To exercise these rights please contact us at service@msaltd.co.uk and we will respond within a month.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added, and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data relating to webpage traffic and customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis, after which the data is removed from the system.
A cookie can only be read by the web server that issued the cookie to you and in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. They are a convenience tool to save you time by speeding up your browsing experience.
Advertisements/Online Marketing
Mass Spec Analytical may serve people who have visited this site with advertisements on our services across the web through Google’s Adwords network.
No personally identifiable information is collected for this purpose or used with this service. Mass Spec Analytical does not use your information to track your browsing habits across the web.
If you wish to opt-out of this service, please visit Google‘s Ads Preferences Manager. You may also want to view the Network Advertising Initiative‘s Consumer Opt-out page.
Links to external sites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, you should note that we do not have any control over these websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and note that such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Information about Children
Our website is not targeted at children and we do not believe we hold any information relating to children.  If you believe we have collected such information please contact us at service@msaltd.co.uk so we may delete this information.
References
General Data Protection Regulations 2017: ICO guidance on GDPR
